Contact

8326540913 (Mobile) cenyellia@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/cenyellia-goodwill-64330b11 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Event Planning
Event Management
Fundraising

Languages

English (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Certified Surgical Services Manager (CSSM)
CNOR

Cenyellia Goodwill

Director Perioperative Services at HCA Houston Healthcare-Pearland

Fresno, Texas

Summary

Servant Leadership

As a nurse, providing comprehensive, compassionate healthcare to the communities we serve. I am fully committed to the care and improvement of human life. Registered Nurse. Specialties: Leadership, Management, Nursing, Decorator, Staging, Interior Design, and Event Planning.

My expertise are to create the perfect venue and ambiance of your event. We work with your budget in mind. A full service event planning company for any and every budget.

Experience

HCA Houston Healthcare-Pearland
Director Perioperative Services
July 2019 - Present (11 months)
Pearland, TX

Responsible for overseeing an Operating Room department with 4 OR suites, 2 Endo suites, PACU, PreOp, Pre-Admit Testing, CSPD and a staff of managers, supervisors, staff Nurses, charge nurses, coordinators, and techs. We see a wide number of cases ranging from general surgery to orthopedic. Responsible for decision-making power over all aspects of the department, including daily operations, patient care, staffing, and budgeting. Maintains a professional relationship with the medical staff at all times and ensures that the needs of the physician, patient and staff are addressed. Participates in all performance improvement processes as well as planning, organization and directing activities of the Perioperative Services according to the policies, procedures, philosophy and objectives of the organization

Mary Kay Global Independent Beauty Consultant April 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months)

Houston, Texas Area

Buzy Bee Wedding Connoisseurs and Event Planners Owner

March 2007 - Present (13 years 3 months)

My position is owner, creative director to create the perfect venue, event, or ambiance. I am the owner of the creative design of the event. Setting up, creating, displaying, decorating, and receptions are my contributions. Whether a wedding reception, birthday party, anniversary, sweet sixteen, date, dinner for 2 or 300, let me create your event for any and every budget with professional and customized services.

HCA Healthcare- Houston Mainland Director of Perioperative Services June 2016 - July 2019 (3 years 2 months) Texas City, TX

Responsible for overseeing an Operating Room department with 6 suites, 3 Endo suites, PACU, Day surgery, Pre-Admit Testing, CSPD and a staff of managers, supervisors, staff Nurses, charge nurses, coordinators, and techs. We see a wide number of cases ranging from general surgery to orthopedic. Responsible for decision-making power over all aspects of the department, including daily operations, patient care, staffing, and budgeting. Maintains a professional relationship with the medical staff at all times and ensures that the needs of the physician, patient and staff are addressed. Participates in all performance improvement processes as well as planning, organization and directing activities of the Perioperative Services according to the policies, procedures, philosophy and objectives of the organization

HCA-Bayshore Medical Center Associate Director of Surgical Serevices November 2015 - June 2016 (8 months) Pasadena, TX

Responsible for overseeing a busy Operating Room department with 10 suites, 2 Endo suites, PACU, Day surgery, Pre-Admit Testing, CSPD and a staff of Staff Nurses, Charge Nurses, and Coordinators. We see a wide number of cases ranging from general surgery to orthopedic and neurosurgery. Assisted with making decisions over all aspects of the department, including daily operations, patient care, staffing, and budgeting. Maintains a professional relationship with the medical staff at all times and ensures that the needs of the physician for patient care are addressed. Participates in all performance improvement processes. Responsible for the planning, organization and directing activities of the Perioperative Services according to the policies,

procedures, philosophy and objectives of the organization. Implemented a Surgical Nurse Navigator which assisted with increasing patient satisfaction scores.

HCA-Clear Lake Regional Medical Center OR Manager March 2014 - November 2015 (1 year 9 months) Webster, Texas

Park Plaza Hospital
Registered Nurse
January 2010 - March 2014 (4 years 3 months)

Kelsey-Seybold Clinic Surgery May 2005 - January 2009 (3 years 9 months)

Education

Western Governors University

Master of Business Administration (M.B.A.), Healthcare

Management · (2016 - 2017)

The University of Texas at Arlington

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2014 - 2015)

Louisiana State University (1989 - 1992)